permadi.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy – permadi.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at permadi@permadi.com.

At permadi.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by permadi.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, permadi.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

permadi.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on permadi.com.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to permadi.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL –<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include [Google Adsense](http://google.com/adsense/) and [ValueClick](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/).These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on permadi.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

permadi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

permadi.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Our Advertising Partners**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include

  * Google
  * ValueClick

_Each of these advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their site._ _  You may consult this listing to find the privacy policy for each of the advertising partners of permadi.com._

  * Google (<https://privacy.google.com/>)
  * ValueClick (<http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy>)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on permadi.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

permadi.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. permadi.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may find a comprehensive listing of these privacy policies and their links here: [Privacy Policy Links](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/privacy-policy-links "Privacy Policy Links").

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. To learn more about cookies, visit <https://cookiesandyou.com/> and [What Are Cookies?](http://www.privacypolicyonline.com/what-are-cookies)

**Children’s Information**  
We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity.  permadi.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that permadi.com has in its database the personally-identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact in the first paragraph) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there.  This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Changes**  
This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes.

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**Update**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, June 1st, 2018.
